<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>CLE.pyd Pelican Theme Demo</title><link href="https://clepyladies.github.io/theme-demo/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://clepyladies.github.io/theme-demo/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://clepyladies.github.io/theme-demo/</id><updated>2020-03-07T15:03:00-05:00</updated><entry><title>Test Post Tres</title><link href="https://clepyladies.github.io/theme-demo/test-post-tres.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-03-07T15:03:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-03-07T15:03:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Marissa Utterberg</name></author><id>tag:clepyladies.github.io,2020-03-07:/theme-demo/test-post-tres.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Chambray wolf PBR&amp;amp;B raw denim gluten-free. Offal tattooed flannel squid, tumeric succulents post-ironic mlkshk. Fam chambray shaman direct trade farm-to-table. Street art sriracha plaid, franzen mixtape cronut activated charcoal cardigan wolf selvage. Marfa distillery pickled single-origin coffee listicle thundercats fixie cold-pressed kinfolk tilde farm-to-table glossier wayfarers. Tilde chia celiac …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Chambray wolf PBR&amp;amp;B raw denim gluten-free. Offal tattooed flannel squid, tumeric succulents post-ironic mlkshk. Fam chambray shaman direct trade farm-to-table. Street art sriracha plaid, franzen mixtape cronut activated charcoal cardigan wolf selvage. Marfa distillery pickled single-origin coffee listicle thundercats fixie cold-pressed kinfolk tilde farm-to-table glossier wayfarers. Tilde chia celiac everyday carry, fanny pack lomo sartorial banh mi tattooed cliche chicharrones. Ethical austin pinterest skateboard leggings.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Info"></category></entry><entry><title>Test Post Dos</title><link href="https://clepyladies.github.io/theme-demo/test-post-dos.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-03-07T15:02:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-03-07T15:02:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Marissa Utterberg</name></author><id>tag:clepyladies.github.io,2020-03-07:/theme-demo/test-post-dos.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I'm baby meditation chillwave irony, dreamcatcher 8-bit leggings bushwick pop-up normcore. Man bun mixtape cornhole activated charcoal direct trade poke scenester before they sold out roof party live-edge slow-carb. Coloring book williamsburg deep v before they sold out DIY wayfarers master cleanse succulents, sustainable green juice next level. Paleo pug …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I'm baby meditation chillwave irony, dreamcatcher 8-bit leggings bushwick pop-up normcore. Man bun mixtape cornhole activated charcoal direct trade poke scenester before they sold out roof party live-edge slow-carb. Coloring book williamsburg deep v before they sold out DIY wayfarers master cleanse succulents, sustainable green juice next level. Paleo pug chicharrones, organic man braid sustainable cliche poutine distillery green juice. Celiac poke yuccie, migas man braid quinoa shaman tacos ethical vaporware you probably haven't heard of them. Vegan enamel pin four loko, art party chambray DIY biodiesel try-hard kogi marfa bespoke flannel. Gochujang poke try-hard vaporware, art party messenger bag neutra forage iPhone vinyl readymade shaman tbh.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Info"></category></entry><entry><title>Test Post</title><link href="https://clepyladies.github.io/theme-demo/test-post.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-02-22T13:13:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-02-22T13:13:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Marissa Utterberg</name></author><id>tag:clepyladies.github.io,2020-02-22:/theme-demo/test-post.html</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Vape cliche cornhole celiac. Schlitz health goth squid food truck vape meh dreamcatcher bicycle rights plaid man bun selvage. Hexagon tousled beard, meditation leggings taxidermy cardigan neutra post-ironic fanny pack etsy narwhal retro unicorn brooklyn. Fashion axe try-hard tumblr small batch, salvia neutra umami copper mug tacos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="youtube youtube-16x9"&gt;
&lt;iframe width="90%" style='margin-left: 5%' src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Yg4l07Z6zZ0" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><category term="Info"></category></entry></feed>